<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en-US">
<link href="https://www.armory.sefeed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" />
<link href="https://www.armory.se/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en-US" />
<id>https://www.armory.se/feed1</id>
<title type="html">Armory</title>
<subtitle>Hyper Speed Metal</subtitle>
<entry> <title type="html">More gigs confirmed</title> <link href="https://armory.se/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="More gigs confirmed" /> <published>2021-09-16</published> <id>More gigs confirmed_2021-09-16</id> <content type="html">
We are finally back in the Milky Way and have now confirmed a bunch of new landing dates:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;2021-10-03: The Abyss, Gothenburg, Sweden&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;2022-01-08: Klubb Fredagsmangel, Stockholm, Sweden&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;2022-01-15: Klubb Dissonans, Jönköping, Sweden (Opening for DARKNESS)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Check out the &lt;a href='/tour'&gt;TOUR&lt;/a&gt; section for our complete flight chart!
</content>
</entry><entry> <title type="html">See you on the road!</title> <link href="https://armory.se/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="See you on the road!" /> <published>2021-06-09</published> <id>See you on the road!_2021-06-09</id> <content type="html">
Finally it seems like we can start playing live again on Planet Earth soon! The first confirmed gig so far will take place in Nässjö, Sweden on August 21th 2021. Awesome support band of the night will be none other than the mighty Commando. More gig announcements to follow... Want us to land in your city? Let us know!
</content>
</entry><entry> <title type="html">Space Marauders 2021</title> <link href="https://armory.se/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Space Marauders 2021" /> <published>2021-01-04</published> <id>Space Marauders 2021_2021-01-04</id> <content type="html">
The 2021 edition of our fanclub, the SPACE MARAUDERS, is now open for registration. Like always, you will get some very exclusive merch as thanks for joining, and you will also continue to support underground speed metal! Your membership will be extra valuable this year, as we will enter Black Path Studios very soon in order to record our next album. Therefore we need all the funds we can get. Head over to the &lt;a href='/fanclub'&gt;FANCLUB&lt;/a&gt; section to read more.
</content>
</entry><entry> <title type="html">Support the underground</title> <link href="https://armory.se/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Support the underground" /> <published>2020-12-07</published> <id>Support the underground_2020-12-07</id> <content type="html">
Unfortunately all gigs except the first one of our Solar System 2020 Tour had to be cancelled/postponed, as you already know. Support underground speed metal by purchasing the tour shirt anyway at &lt;a href='https://www.jawbreaker.se/product/armory-2020-tour-t-shirt/'&gt;Jawbreaker.se&lt;/a&gt;!
</content>
</entry><entry> <title type="html">Show With Darkness Rescheduled</title> <link href="https://armory.se/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Show With Darkness Rescheduled" /> <published>2020-11-20</published> <id>Show With Darkness Rescheduled_2020-11-20</id> <content type="html">
We have our first gig for 2022 already secured. It's the show together with thrash legends Darkness in Jönköping, that was originally planned to take place in April 2020, that has now been rescheduled to January 2022. (We are in the big league now, booking gigs over a year in advance).
</content>
</entry><entry> <title type="html">New Restrictions</title> <link href="https://armory.se/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="New Restrictions" /> <published>2020-11-16</published> <id>New Restrictions_2020-11-16</id> <content type="html">
Thanks for the wild night in Malmö last Saturday, Marauders! The city will probably take a long time to rebuild again. Unfortunately our upcoming shows in Motala and Nässjö will have to be cancelled/postponed due to the new and stricter restrictions from the Swedish government. We will let you know as soon as the restrictions are lifted again. We will return!
</content>
</entry><entry> <title type="html">Upcoming Album And Live Gigs!</title> <link href="https://armory.se/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Upcoming Album And Live Gigs!" /> <published>2020-09-20</published> <id>Upcoming Album And Live Gigs!_2020-09-20</id> <content type="html">
Greetings Marauders! You haven't heard from us in a while... That is because we have been busy writing our new album! It will be a concept album and will be recorded early next year. To wet your appetite though, we have decided to do a small tour this November and play the upcoming album in its enterity!!! Go to the &lt;a href='/tour'&gt;TOUR&lt;/a&gt; section to see all the upcoming dates. Stay fast!
</content>
</entry><entry> <title type="html">A Message From Space</title> <link href="https://armory.se/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Message From Space" /> <published>2020-04-10</published> <id>A Message From Space_2020-04-10</id> <content type="html">
Unfortunately but not surprisingly our gig at The Abyss together with Ambush has been postponed to an unknown date. As all of our concerts are either cancelled or postponed, we stand without income at the moment. If you would like to show your support you can join our fanclub for just 100 SEK and you will get a killer fanclub package in return. &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://www.jawbreaker.se/product/space-marauders-membership/'&gt;Follow this hyperlink to read more&lt;/a&gt;.
</content>
</entry><entry> <title type="html">Space Marauders 2020</title> <link href="https://armory.se/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Space Marauders 2020" /> <published>2020-03-22</published> <id>Space Marauders 2020_2020-03-22</id> <content type="html">
The 2020 edition of the Space Marauders, also known as the fastest fanclub in the known universe, is now open for registration. As usual, membership is only 100 SEK and included in the price is a very special gift. We know we say this every year, but this year's secret will be something extraordinary indeed! If you are ready to step into the unknown, &lt;a href='https://www.jawbreaker.se/product/space-marauders-membership/'&gt;follow this hyperlink&lt;/a&gt;.
</content>
</entry><entry> <title type="html">Outbreak of Evil</title> <link href="https://armory.se/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Outbreak of Evil" /> <published>2020-03-20</published> <id>Outbreak of Evil_2020-03-20</id> <content type="html">
Unfortunately our gig with Darkness on 2020-04-04 has been cancelled due to the current quarantine situation on Sol III. Our gig with Ambush in Gothenburg on 2020-04-17 is still on though so make sure to get your tickets &lt;a href='https://www.tickster.com/sv/events/avbm5ce4l51ue7g/2020-04-17/ambush-armory'&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;!
</content>
</entry><entry> <title type="html">4/17</title> <link href="https://armory.se/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="4/17" /> <published>2020-03-01</published> <id>4/17_2020-03-01</id> <content type="html">
This year we are gonna celebrate the official speed metal island day (April 17th or 4/17) at The Abyss in Gothenburg together with reigning heavy metal champions Ambush from Småland. Ambush are in turn celebrating the release of their third album &lt;span class='title'&gt;Infidel&lt;/span&gt;, out on High Roller Records, so this will be a night to remember. The gig is expected to sell out to make sure to get your tickets in advance. &lt;p&gt; &lt;a href='https://www.tickster.com/sv/events/avbm5ce4l51ue7g/2020-04-17/ambush-armory'&gt;Tickets available here.&lt;/a&gt;
</content>
</entry><entry> <title type="html">We are opening for DARKNESS!</title> <link href="https://armory.se/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="We are opening for DARKNESS!" /> <published>2019-11-29</published> <id>We are opening for DARKNESS!_2019-11-29</id> <content type="html">
On the 4th of April 2020 we will return to Jönköping, Småland together with the mighty DARKNESS from Germany. See you there speedfreekz! &lt;p&gt; &lt;a href='https://www.tickster.com/sv/events/12jmb53emx4wfw2/2020-04-04/darkness-armory-klubb-dissonans'&gt;Read more and get your tickets here!&lt;/a&gt;
</content>
</entry><entry> <title type="html">Metal Magic</title> <link href="https://armory.se/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Metal Magic" /> <published>2019-07-01</published> <id>Metal Magic_2019-07-01</id> <content type="html">
Soon we will head over to Denmark for our first show on Danish ground ever. The location will be non other than the legendary Metal Magic Festival in Fredericia on July 11-13th. Our gig is on Friday the 12th, but beware that we will stay for the whole festival and have a wild time with everyone! See you there! &lt;p&gt; &lt;a href='http://metal-magic.dk/'&gt;Read more and get your tickets here!&lt;/a&gt;
</content>
</entry><entry> <title type="html">Noselake Metal Festival</title> <link href="https://armory.se/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Noselake Metal Festival" /> <published>2019-05-25</published> <id>Noselake Metal Festival_2019-05-25</id> <content type="html">
On June the 28th we will return once more to Småland, this time to lay waste to the town of Nässjö at Noselake Metal Festival. Two days of heavy metal with many killer bands!&lt;br&gt; &lt;a href='https://secure.tickster.com/sv/wz6ztumev1t8wyu/products'&gt;Get your tickets here!&lt;/a&gt;
</content>
</entry><entry> <title type="html">Armory Online</title> <link href="https://armory.se/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Armory Online" /> <published>2019-05-17</published> <id>Armory Online_2019-05-17</id> <content type="html">
Website launched.
</content>
</entry><entry> <title type="html">Music Video</title> <link href="https://armory.se/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Music Video" /> <published>2018-10-04</published> <id>Music Video_2018-10-04</id> <content type="html">
Our first music video is out now! The song is &lt;span class='title'&gt;Vault Seven&lt;/span&gt; from our latest album &lt;span class='title'&gt;The Search&lt;/span&gt;, out now through High Roller Records. The video was directed by the mighty Jim Nedergård and is a dark story about invisible enemies, paranoia and the dangerous power of forbidden knowledge. &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UYj3EnEON8k'&gt;Watch it here!&lt;/a&gt;
</content>
</entry><entry> <title type="html">The Search Out Today!</title> <link href="https://armory.se/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Search Out Today!" /> <published>2018-07-13</published> <id>The Search Out Today!_2018-07-13</id> <content type="html">
It is Friday the 13th and our second full-length album &lt;span class='title'&gt;The Search&lt;/span&gt; is released today by High Roller Records!
</content>
</entry></feed>